one two three
ring
hey excuse me for a minute before we
begin
i want you to please please please read
the product knowledge of this mock call
do not skip to the mock call without
reading the product knowledge
i promise you fifty percent of your
success in passing your mock call test
depends on your ability to comprehend
the product knowledge
before the mock call so please do
yourself a favor
and take a minute or two to read and
understand this mock cost product
knowledge
okay so here it goes
hi thank you for calling hotel
california this is candice how may i
help you
hi candice this is steven i'd like to
book for
four people please and that would be
for august 18th
sure stephen i'd be happy to help you
with that so
which room do you have in mind actually
i gotta tell you first
that i am super busy so
i haven't been able to browse through
your website and i don't know
i don't really know the rooms you have
right now
but i could give you my requirements and
then
you suggest the best rooms for me
could we do that absolutely what do you
need
so there are four of us
including me and we need something with
a wi-fi
and maybe a swimming pool got it
will you four be staying in one room or
separate rooms
oh sorry i forgot to tell you um
that would be separate because you see
we're two couples so we need two rooms
i see so in that case i
recommend two deluxe kings
each room has a king-sized bed which
fits two people
a wi-fi and access to a swimming pool
and free lunch and breakfast all of
these
for two hundred dollars each and that's
gonna be
four hundred dollars for for two rooms
how does it sound
oh that is a bit too much
that's a bit expensive actually do you
maybe have something
more affordable than that it's just not
now that i think about it
i remember there's a beach close to your
hotel so we will
probably just take a trip there and you
can take out the swimming pool
is that possible sure let me see your
options here
so if you want to take out the swimming
pool
and just have the wi-fi then we
certainly have a room for that
and that is the classic king for 125
each which is 250 for two rooms as
opposed to 400
and you're still gonna get the king-size
bed and the wi-fi
but i have to tell you steven aside from
having no swimming pool
you will also only get a free breakfast
instead of
lunch and breakfast is that okay with
you
perfect perfect candice that's exactly
what we need
we'll be having lunch at the beach
anyways so we won't be eating at the
hotel
so two classic king it is uh do you need
my credit card number
or what do you need uh for security
purposes we don't really take credit
card info over the phone
but what i need from you instead is your
email address
where i can send you a link where you
can
securely pay and enter your card
information
okay cool you can send it to steven
underscore 182 at gmail.com
thank you how do you spell stephen by
the way is that a steven with a v
or a steven with a p that's with a p
for pepper thank you
so just to make sure let me just spell
that out for you that is
s for sierra t for tango e for echo
p for peter h for hotel and for nancy
underscore 182 at
gmail.com yep that's correct
okay perfect so
just to recap you will be booking
two classic kings for this august
18th 2020 and the total amount is
250 dollars for two rooms are all of
these correct
yep all correct thank you steven
so after this call you should receive an
email from
booking at calihotel.com and that email
is a secure link
where you can click and enter your full
name
and card info i also want to remind you
not to click
any of the email that is not from
booking calihotel.com
because we only take payments through
this one email all right
gotcha so is there anything else that i
can help you with today
nope you've been very helpful candace
thank you so much you're most welcome
steven thank you for calling hotel
california you have a great day
have a great day candice bye
if you want a detailed explanation of
what is said during the call and the
call flow
from start to middle to finish
check the description below because i
have attached
the link of the video where i
included a detailed explanation of what
was going on
during this muck call this is especially
important
if you are a call center newbie this
could
really be a lot to take in and the
explanation in the video will help you
make sense of everything that goes on in
the makkal so that's
it if you like this video consider
subscribing and liking this video
bye thank you for watching